

+91-9533668305

🗹 ajaychinnam7@gmail.com

O HYDERABAD, TELANGANA

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/ajay-ch-41784a171/

https://bit.ly/3F4RiJM

https://github.com/Ajaych7

#### **SUMMARY**

Ambitious Java Developer versed in following established procedures and working under little or no supervision. Offering technical expertise in programming analysis, application analysis and design. Excellent team player with in-depth knowledge of development tools and languages.

# WORK EXPERIENCE

Oct 2021 - Present

# Associate – Computer Vision Randstand , HYDERABAD

LiDAR accuracy data Traffic Light, Sign & Possible States involving lane marking, annotation and validation features.

- NVMAP RT editor 3D Map labelling box
- Autonomous vehicle Navigation Issue Tracking,
- Lane Channels to Driver Comfort rating indicating detect semantic road features
- providing clues model optimize training-time parameters in order to improve overall quality
- Facilitated construction by mapping out utility installations and establishing reference points, grades and elevations.

#### Sep 2020 - Jul 2021

# Associate – Computer Vision ADWAIT Algorithm , HYDERABAD

- IMAGE POI -Face, Head and Body Bounding Box
- Video Tech Clues-Shot verification, Scene, Credits and Frames
- TEXTRACT.-Segmentation,Content area and label identification
- Audio Task-timestamp,total duration,speaker ids and background noise
- Transformed project data requirements into project data models.

# Apr 2019 - Oct 2019

## Data Analyst DEEPEN AI , HYDERABAD

- Completed LiDAR data involving lane making, polyline annotation and validation features.
- 2D&3D Bounding box
- Autonomous vehicle Navigation,
- · Object detection and tracking
- Participated in requirements meetings and data mapping sessions to understand business needs.
- Corrected any data entry error to prevent later issues such as duplication or data degradation.

## **SKILLS**

Programming languages :C,Core java

Operating system: Window, Linux

60.58%

Database : SQL

Web Technology: HTML5 ,CSS3,Bootstrap, javascript.

## **EDUCATION**

Sep 2014 - May 2018

bachelor of technology: computer science and engineering

Anurag group of institution

# **PROJECTS**

### Oil Price Prediction Using Machine Learning Algorithm

The aim of this project is forcecasting crude oil prices using Support Vector Algorithm (SVR) Algorithm to determine the optimal parameters in the model using the SVR, is a grid search algorithm divides the range of parameters to be optimised into the grid and across all points to the optimal parameters.

#### **SPEAKERFREAKS**

Website Music portal :Speakerfreaks is to entertain the user can listen, download ,upload an also included lyrics of different songs and gets notification new songs are added.

www.speakerfreaks.anuragweb.club

## **CERTIFICATIONS**

#### **EFSET**

EFSET English Certificate 88/100 C2 Proficient EF Standard English Test (https://www.efset.org/cert/xTcKFT)

#### **Ethical Hacking Tool**

Completion Certificate By Kyrion Technologies in NIT Warangal. conducted a three day workshop on 'Ethical Hacking'